{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:I..I.all.10.rand.say.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781144790","data":{"timestamp":" 946781144789"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" a5170085-e3a4-4e66-ab9c-6d0f39ce2fd2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_I_A-U-I"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781156754","data":{"timestamp":" 946781156753"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781157001","data":{"timestamp":" 946781157001"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781157453","data":{"timestamp":" 946781157452"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781157902","data":{"timestamp":" 946781157902"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781158231","data":{"timestamp":" 946781158231"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781159037","data":{"timestamp":" 946781159037"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781159649","data":{"timestamp":" 946781159647"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781159900","data":{"timestamp":" 946781159900"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781160707","data":{"timestamp":" 946781160705"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781163436","data":{"timestamp":" 946781163435"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781164425","data":{"timestamp":" 946781164425"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781164865","data":{"timestamp":" 946781164865"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781165054","data":{"timestamp":" 946781165053"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781165664","data":{"timestamp":" 946781165662"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781168807","data":{"timestamp":" 946781168806"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILITOA"," userResponse":" ILITOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781169443","data":{"timestamp":" 946781169442"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781170215","data":{"timestamp":" 946781170214"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781173301","data":{"timestamp":" 946781173300"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781173977","data":{"timestamp":" 946781173976"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781174839","data":{"timestamp":" 946781174839"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781175063","data":{"timestamp":" 946781175063"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781175817","data":{"timestamp":" 946781175817"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781176671","data":{"timestamp":" 946781176671"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781177754","data":{"timestamp":" 946781177754"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781178780","data":{"timestamp":" 946781178779"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKWENDA"," userResponse":" TUTAKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781179705","data":{"timestamp":" 946781179705"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781180788","data":{"timestamp":" 946781180787"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781181222","data":{"timestamp":" 946781181222"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781181881","data":{"timestamp":" 946781181881"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781182056","data":{"timestamp":" 946781182056"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781182652","data":{"timestamp":" 946781182652"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781185916","data":{"timestamp":" 946781185916"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781187080","data":{"timestamp":" 946781187079"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781187814","data":{"timestamp":" 946781187814"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781191219","data":{"timestamp":" 946781191219"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESAFIRIA"," userResponse":" ANGESAFIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781191832","data":{"timestamp":" 946781191832"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781192255","data":{"timestamp":" 946781192255"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781192759","data":{"timestamp":" 946781192759"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781193243","data":{"timestamp":" 946781193242"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781193456","data":{"timestamp":" 946781193455"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781194157","data":{"timestamp":" 946781194157"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781197089","data":{"timestamp":" 946781197088"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781197666","data":{"timestamp":" 946781197666"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781198205","data":{"timestamp":" 946781198205"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781198664","data":{"timestamp":" 946781198663"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781201896","data":{"timestamp":" 946781201896"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781202663","data":{"timestamp":" 946781202662"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781203613","data":{"timestamp":" 946781203612"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781204962","data":{"timestamp":" 946781204962"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEVAA"," userResponse":" AMEVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781205631","data":{"timestamp":" 946781205631"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781206010","data":{"timestamp":" 946781206010"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781206545","data":{"timestamp":" 946781206544"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781207621","data":{"timestamp":" 946781207621"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" ALIKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781207679","data":{"timestamp":" 946781207679"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781207770","data":{"timestamp":" 946781207769"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 8d5954b7-a9a5-4fec-9bda-79fe50ee721e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alikuwa tayari amevaa wakati mama yake alikwenda kumuamsha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" ALIKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781219896","data":{"timestamp":" 946781219896"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 4ffa1d7b-e44e-43ea-ac4f-aba983bfa393"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781221083","data":{"timestamp":" 946781221083"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 4ffa1d7b-e44e-43ea-ac4f-aba983bfa393"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781221220","data":{"timestamp":" 946781221220"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 4ffa1d7b-e44e-43ea-ac4f-aba983bfa393"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::numbers_counting_song__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781228113","data":{"timestamp":" 946781228112"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 4ffa1d7b-e44e-43ea-ac4f-aba983bfa393"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781235305","data":{"timestamp":" 946781235304"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 4ffa1d7b-e44e-43ea-ac4f-aba983bfa393"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781245894","data":{"timestamp":" 946781245893"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 4ffa1d7b-e44e-43ea-ac4f-aba983bfa393"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781254107","data":{"timestamp":" 946781254106"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 4ffa1d7b-e44e-43ea-ac4f-aba983bfa393"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781279447","data":{"timestamp":" 946781279447"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 785ab389-1376-49bd-a244-736cc03c5ed3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-2-8"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781285752","data":{"timestamp":" 946781285752"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 785ab389-1376-49bd-a244-736cc03c5ed3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_4-8-1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781293431","data":{"timestamp":" 946781293430"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 785ab389-1376-49bd-a244-736cc03c5ed3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_9-7-0"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781298455","data":{"timestamp":" 946781298455"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 785ab389-1376-49bd-a244-736cc03c5ed3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_9-7-0"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781303992","data":{"timestamp":" 946781303991"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 785ab389-1376-49bd-a244-736cc03c5ed3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-2-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781309110","data":{"timestamp":" 946781309110"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 785ab389-1376-49bd-a244-736cc03c5ed3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-2-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781313726","data":{"timestamp":" 946781313726"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 785ab389-1376-49bd-a244-736cc03c5ed3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-2-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781323169","data":{"timestamp":" 946781323169"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 785ab389-1376-49bd-a244-736cc03c5ed3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_9-5-2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781329193","data":{"timestamp":" 946781329193"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 785ab389-1376-49bd-a244-736cc03c5ed3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781343952","data":{"timestamp":" 946781343951"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 785ab389-1376-49bd-a244-736cc03c5ed3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781352321","data":{"timestamp":" 946781352320"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 785ab389-1376-49bd-a244-736cc03c5ed3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781369745","data":{"timestamp":" 946781369745"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 66b68dfe-0670-4434-b89c-59d9988a8151"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_9-7-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781376212","data":{"timestamp":" 946781376211"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 66b68dfe-0670-4434-b89c-59d9988a8151"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_9-7-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781381286","data":{"timestamp":" 946781381286"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 66b68dfe-0670-4434-b89c-59d9988a8151"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_9-7-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781386477","data":{"timestamp":" 946781386476"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 66b68dfe-0670-4434-b89c-59d9988a8151"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_9-7-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781397702","data":{"timestamp":" 946781397702"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" cfc71978-4674-4740-a86b-a97dfadb7d63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JASHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JASHO"," userResponse":" JASHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781400395","data":{"timestamp":" 946781400395"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" cfc71978-4674-4740-a86b-a97dfadb7d63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JASHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JASHO"," userResponse":" JASHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781401949","data":{"timestamp":" 946781401949"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" cfc71978-4674-4740-a86b-a97dfadb7d63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIWE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781408787","data":{"timestamp":" 946781408787"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" cfc71978-4674-4740-a86b-a97dfadb7d63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIWE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781410405","data":{"timestamp":" 946781410405"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" cfc71978-4674-4740-a86b-a97dfadb7d63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781416115","data":{"timestamp":" 946781416115"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" cfc71978-4674-4740-a86b-a97dfadb7d63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" START_JIKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781417127","data":{"timestamp":" 946781417127"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" cfc71978-4674-4740-a86b-a97dfadb7d63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781418736","data":{"timestamp":" 946781418736"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" cfc71978-4674-4740-a86b-a97dfadb7d63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JICHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781421871","data":{"timestamp":" 946781421870"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" cfc71978-4674-4740-a86b-a97dfadb7d63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JICHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781423432","data":{"timestamp":" 946781423431"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" cfc71978-4674-4740-a86b-a97dfadb7d63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" JANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781425314","data":{"timestamp":" 946781425314"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" cfc71978-4674-4740-a86b-a97dfadb7d63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" JANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781425494","data":{"timestamp":" 946781425494"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" cfc71978-4674-4740-a86b-a97dfadb7d63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" JANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781432184","data":{"timestamp":" 946781432184"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" cfc71978-4674-4740-a86b-a97dfadb7d63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" JANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781439401","data":{"timestamp":" 946781439401"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" cfc71978-4674-4740-a86b-a97dfadb7d63"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" JANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781452774","data":{"timestamp":" 946781452774"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" ce1e4183-a5f5-4976-9662-bd0181f73433"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_7-2-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781461705","data":{"timestamp":" 946781461705"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" ce1e4183-a5f5-4976-9662-bd0181f73433"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-2-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781473767","data":{"timestamp":" 946781473767"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" ce1e4183-a5f5-4976-9662-bd0181f73433"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-4-9"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781478909","data":{"timestamp":" 946781478908"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" ce1e4183-a5f5-4976-9662-bd0181f73433"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-4-9"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781489675","data":{"timestamp":" 946781489675"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" ce1e4183-a5f5-4976-9662-bd0181f73433"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_7-5-9"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781495766","data":{"timestamp":" 946781495765"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" ce1e4183-a5f5-4976-9662-bd0181f73433"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_7-5-9"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781500749","data":{"timestamp":" 946781500749"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" ce1e4183-a5f5-4976-9662-bd0181f73433"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_7-5-9"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781501701","data":{"timestamp":" 946781501699"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" ce1e4183-a5f5-4976-9662-bd0181f73433"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.mc.41"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_5_7-5-9"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781520032","data":{"timestamp":" 946781520032"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781520406","data":{"timestamp":" 946781520406"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781520890","data":{"timestamp":" 946781520890"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781521233","data":{"timestamp":" 946781521233"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781521637","data":{"timestamp":" 946781521637"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781522110","data":{"timestamp":" 946781522109"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781522335","data":{"timestamp":" 946781522335"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781525554","data":{"timestamp":" 946781525554"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781525593","data":{"timestamp":" 946781525593"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781526306","data":{"timestamp":" 946781526306"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781526699","data":{"timestamp":" 946781526699"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781526992","data":{"timestamp":" 946781526992"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781527194","data":{"timestamp":" 946781527194"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781527389","data":{"timestamp":" 946781527389"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781527704","data":{"timestamp":" 946781527704"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781527928","data":{"timestamp":" 946781527928"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781531115","data":{"timestamp":" 946781531114"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781531521","data":{"timestamp":" 946781531520"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781534109","data":{"timestamp":" 946781534108"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781534314","data":{"timestamp":" 946781534313"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781534521","data":{"timestamp":" 946781534520"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781537940","data":{"timestamp":" 946781537940"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781541625","data":{"timestamp":" 946781541623"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781542659","data":{"timestamp":" 946781542659"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781545375","data":{"timestamp":" 946781545375"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781545756","data":{"timestamp":" 946781545755"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781546246","data":{"timestamp":" 946781546246"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781546595","data":{"timestamp":" 946781546595"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781547006","data":{"timestamp":" 946781547006"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781547485","data":{"timestamp":" 946781547485"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781547717","data":{"timestamp":" 946781547717"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781550947","data":{"timestamp":" 946781550945"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781550999","data":{"timestamp":" 946781550998"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781551723","data":{"timestamp":" 946781551722"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781552126","data":{"timestamp":" 946781552125"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781552431","data":{"timestamp":" 946781552430"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781552641","data":{"timestamp":" 946781552641"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781552842","data":{"timestamp":" 946781552842"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781553161","data":{"timestamp":" 946781553161"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781553389","data":{"timestamp":" 946781553388"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781556057","data":{"timestamp":" 946781556056"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781556182","data":{"timestamp":" 946781556182"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781568351","data":{"timestamp":" 946781568350"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781583107","data":{"timestamp":" 946781583107"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" 15bc5412-c859-4e54-a7fa-f643c86ecd03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781602504","data":{"timestamp":" 946781602504"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" c19a11bc-6d61-4876-98b3-20789a253c66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946781603306","data":{"timestamp":" 946781603305"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000102_054536"," gameId":" c19a11bc-6d61-4876-98b3-20789a253c66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}